e-games.com.ph 2010-12-23

# IP e-Games Privacy Policy « E-Games Portal

Intellectual Property Ventures Group is an online games company that strives to provide unique gaming experiences through innovation and advanced game technology. We are constantly improving current system functions and developing new systems to ensure the best gaming experience for our customers. We are committed to providing our customers with the widest variety of online games available. Intellectual Property Ventures Group has an extensive catalogue of games to reach players of all ages, interests and regions of the world, and promises to bring them never before experienced exciting entertainment. For more information on Intellectual Property Ventures Group go to: http://www.ipvg.com

**Overall privacy statement**

We take your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to all e-Games related sites.

**What information do we collect?**

Personally identifiable information that we collect from a user include the first and last name of the user, e-mail address, identification card number, address, phone number and fax number. Non-personally identifiable information that we collect from a user include country, date of birth, gender and marital status. However, the user may or may not decide to provide us with his or her address, identification card number, marital status, phone number or fax number.

Additionally, when visitors come to our site, we automatically collect some non-personally identifiable “computer” information, such as the type of computer operating system (e.g., Windows 95 or Mac OS), the web browser (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer) being used, and information regarding the Internet service provider.

**What we do with the information collected, how we use it.**

We use the names and e-mail addresses of subscribers to our e-mail newsletter only to send them the newsletter. Each newsletter contains instructions on how to be removed from the subscription list.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site, to personalize our visitors’ experience on all websites belonging to Intellectual Property Ventures Group., and to offer products, programs, and services. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services.

We cannot ensure that your private communications and other personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.

Additionally, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to investigate or resolve possible problems or inquiries.

Furthermore, if you request any technical support, you consent to our remote accessing and review of the computer you load the Software onto for purposes of support and debugging. You agree that we may communicate with you via email and any similar technology for any purpose relating to the Game, the Software and any services or software which may in the future be provided by us or on our behalf.

Since we do not control other web sites and/or privacy policies of third parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to others. You acknowledge and agree that we may transfer your account information (including your personally identifiable information and other data) to Philippines or other countries or may share such information with our licensees and agents in connection with the Game.

**Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect on-line.

**What are our practices regarding cookies**

The e-Games Portal uses a software technology called “cookies.” Cookies are small text files that we and certain third parties place in visitors’ computer browsers to store their preferences. Cookies themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information. Although cookies could enable us to relate a visitor’s use of this Web site to personal information that a visitor has provided, such as an e-mail address, we do not use them for this purpose. We do use “cookies” to determine how many visitors we have and how often they visit various sections of our site.

**Contact us**

Questions regarding our Privacy Policy can be directed to:

Intellectual Property Ventures Group,  
34th Flr. Tower 2 RCBC Plaza,  
6819 Ayala Ave., Makati City 1200  
Metro Manila, Philippines

Telephone Number : (632) 886 7821  
Facsimile Number: (632) 886 6510  
Email Address: [helpdesk@e-games.com.ph](mailto:helpdesk@e-games.com.ph)
